{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2159","name":"Roberts Riverwalk Hotel","address":"1000 River Place","zipcode":"48207","owner":"Roberts Hotels Detroit, LLC","licenseNumber":"069140","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.01473,42.33666","geojson":{"id":"2159","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.014727858,42.3366556660001]},"properties":{"name":"Roberts Riverwalk Hotel","owner":"Roberts Hotels Detroit, LLC","address":"1000 River Place","zipcode":"48207","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"069140","establishmentid":"2159","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5319","name":"Cranks","address":"200 Walker","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"4410","name":"Detroit Affordable Assisted Living","address":"3103 Wight St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"51622625","name":"Morrison Community Living @ Rivertown","address":"250 McDougall St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"4389","name":"Snake Bites","address":"300 River Place","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1450","name":"Rattlesnake Club","address":"300 River Place","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1247","name":"Andrew's on the Corner","address":"201 Joseph Campau Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"3974","name":"River Place Bar & Grill","address":"225 Joseph Campau","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5143","name":"Atwater Brewery","address":"237 Joseph Campau St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"4387","name":"Detroit Academy of Arts & Sciences MS","address":"3100 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","address":"3242 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44782","inspectionDate":"2019-01-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"ceiling(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Smooth","location":"OFFICE","subLocation":"Missing Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."}]},{"inspectionid":"42678","inspectionDate":"2018-06-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTAURANT BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"40943","inspectionDate":"2017-11-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Missing Digital Thermometer","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."}]},{"inspectionid":"39846","inspectionDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"38870","inspectionDate":"2017-06-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint/Routine","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Adulterated/contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Under the Condenser","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Under the Condenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"38162","inspectionDate":"2017-02-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Over head spray unit ","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Behind the Cooler (bar)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Faucet handles of hand wash sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ENTIRE FACILITY","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"36140","inspectionDate":"2016-08-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Drip Tray","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Bulk food bins","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"doors","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Door of freezer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Water filter","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Behind the Condenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2159"}}